

Muhammad Afryan Saputra

Bojongsoang, Bandung, Jawa Barat, 40288

😃 : 21 April 2022

📞 : (+62) 812-2006-1316

LinkedIn ←

GitHub ←

Streamlit

Summary

Bachelor's degree in Informatics Engineering at Telkom University with a Data Science concentration and 240+ hours of internship experience at UPTD PSDA WS Cisadea-Cibareno, 500+ hours working on projects in data science and data analysis throughout 2023.

Education

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering (Informatics Engineering), Telkom University, Indonesia

2019-2023

- GPA: 3.04
- EPRT: 510
- Final-Project research entitled: "Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis Using Recurrent Neural Networks (RNN) on Social Media
- Presenting Final-Project in "The 6th International Conference on Data Science and Its Applications 2023"

Work Experience

Mobile Application Developer, UPTD PSDA WS Cisadea-Cibareno, Indonesia | Internship

07/2022 - 09/2022

- Utilized Python scripting to efficiently organize and process employee data, resulting in a 22% reduction in data processing time
- Designed and implemented an SQL database system to store employee information, improving data accessibility and retrieval
- Created visually appealing Employee of the Month displays using Canva, contributing to a 17% increase in employee morale and engagement.
- Successfully coordinated projects involving Python, MySQL, Canva, and Flutter, demonstrating proficiency in integrating technologies for a seamless workflow.

Assistant Lecturer, Telkom University, Indonesia

07/2022 - 09/2022

- Conducted regular assessments, resulting in a 35% decrease in students struggling with foundational programming principles.
- Achieved a 15% increase in the number of students completing advanced programming projects successfully.
- Implemented a training session support system resulting in a 30% decrease in lecturer workload.

Skills

Programming : Python, GoLang Data Processing/Wrangling : SQL, Pandas, NumPy Data Visualization : Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly

Machine Learning : Scikit-Learn

: TensorFlow, PvTorch, Keras Deep Learning

Mobile Development : Flutter

Web Development : Laravel, HTML, CSS : Streamlit, Heroku Model Deployment